hey guys here's a fun Little Riddle That
I came up with earlier this week it's
asking you to solve for x and this looks
a lot like the quadratic formula but
it's a little different if you want to
try to solve it on your own pause right
now I'm going to show how I would
approach this in three two one so first
off this is the actual quadratic formula
I'm given that this will solve for x but
I also know for a fact this will solve
for x it looks like a has literally just
been substituted for all the other
letters and it looks like we've also
plugged in a for two so I think we can
say that a equals two I'm going to plug
in 2 for all the places of a then I can
simplify things a little bit simplify a
little bit more it's a little weird
right here because we have a negative
under the square root and the way we
handle that negative one of the square
root is y top and bottom are both
divisible by two and this is an answer
to the question and we can put a box
around that is there another approach we
can take to find another value of x how
exciting